watchit.com 2014-03-22

# Privacy Policy - Smartpros - eCampus

## Your Privacy

SmartPros aims to offer the highest quality online experience to its customers, and values our customers' privacy and personal information provided to enable us to do so. 

We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information such as email address, name and mailing address to third parties without our customers' consent to do so. For example, in conjunction with contests or special promotions, customers may opt to receive information from companies with relevant products, services or resources. Only at such time and with our customers' permission, may third parties have access to this personal information. 

Additionally, all email communications from SmartPros, such as email newsletters and special alerts, provide details for customers on how to easily add or remove their contact information from our communications programs. 

### Website Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred by a Web site to a computer's hard drive. We send cookies when you visit our site, make purchases, or respond to online surveys or polls. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your personal information. The aggregate information collected enables us to analyze traffic patterns on our site, and maintain your user session on our e-commerce and restricted-access Web sites such as the eCampus.com. Specifically, cookies enable you to enter your username and password only once on pages where a login is required.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies, or selectively accept certain cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If cookies are turned off though, there may be some features of our site that will not be available and some Web pages may not display properly. For more information on adjusting your cookie settings, go to the Help menu of your browser.
